We was already consumed with racist.
Now we learn about the Zionist, which is really still racist, but with a twist.
We thought we had Republicans versus Democrats.
Now we see we just have a bunch of capitalists.
Thought that we had the right and left, but we just have fake liberals and fascists.
And when you add all of it up, it's a bunch of bullshit.
I'm looking around and I don't like any part of this government.
It's going to take something drastic.
Don't know what that is, but it's going to take something drastic.
Alien landing.
Yes, it's going to take something drastic to change.
Because that's how change happens.
That's how change happens.
And I know it's going to come from the kids.
Yep.
You know why?
Because their minds are still free and they can imagine.
They can imagine ungirded, unfettered, without the limitations of those of us with experience.
And so we must support and fortify them with what they need to imagine a better future for themselves.
And so we're going to take a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little